Kebab & Horoscope is a comedy, drama film directed by Grzegorz Jaroszuk.
A group of misfits from a carpet shop have a chance to change their lives with the help of two
marketing experts - an ex-kebab shop worker and an ex-fortune teller from a wildlife magazine.
'Kebab', played by Bartłomiej Topa.
'Horoskop', played by Piotr Żurawski.
Cashier, played by Barbara Jonak.
Ex Fan, played by Tomasz Schuchardt.
Intern, played by Justyna Wasilewska.
Miłość matki stażystki, played by Marek Kalita.
Justyna Wasilewska (Polish pronunciation: [jusˈtɘ.na
va.ɕiˈlɛf.ska]; born 28 November 1985) is a Polish actress.
The film explores themes of marketing, misfit, expert.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.